entropiaforum.com 2007-06-23

# EntropiaForum Privacy Policy - EntropiaForum

EF Owner  
Administrator

Joined: Aug 06

Gender:  Ingame: 

Location: EntropiaForum

Posts: 1,613  
EFD: 151,089     Donate

Fame: 44 

Reputation: Impressive   
Achievements: [2](http://www.entropiaforum.com/forums/search.php?do=process&starteronly=1&searchuser=711&childforums=1&exactname=1&forumchoice\[\]=9)

| 

**EntropiaForum Privacy Policy**

* * *

ENTROPIAFORUM.COM PRIVACY POLICY

 **GENERAL INFORMATION:**

EntropiaForum.com (hereinafter "EntropiaForum") and its administrators, moderators and/or agents (hereinafter "Staff"), values the privacy of its users, registered members, and others who visit and use (collectively or individually, hereinafter "Members") [www.EntropiaForum.com](http://www.entropiaforum.com/) and any other web sites or services owned or operated by EntropiaForum.com. 

EntropiaForum respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. 

Any personal information you provide on EntropiaForum remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Forum Rules. The date of the latest version of this Policy is indicated at the bottom of this page.

EntropiaForum will never use your contact information to send unsolicited commercial messages ("spam"), nor will EntropiaForum ever disclose your contact information for such purposes.

NOTE TO KIDS: EntropiaForum is NOT intended for persons under the age of 13 years. If you are under 13 years of age, then we encourage you to visit web sites more suited to a younger audience.

**NEVER DISPLAY ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT COULD BE USED TO FIND YOU IN THE REAL WORLD** \- for example, your full legal name, mailing or home address, or telephone numbers.

**NEVER TRANSMIT ANY OF YOUR ENTROPIA UNIVERSE ACCOUNT INFORMATION TO ANOTHER FORUM MEMBER, ADMINISTRATOR OR MODERATOR.** EntropiaForum Staff will NEVER ask for such information.

 **THE INFORMATION ENTROPIAFORUM COLLECTS:**

Member-provided Information: You may provide to EntropiaForum what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number, etc.) when you register as a Member and if you participate in certain activities on EntropiaForum. In addition, you may choose to post certain information to your public "profile" on EntropiaForum such as your date of birth, general location, interests, occupation, web site URLs, videos, blogs, IM addresses, and comments. 

"Cookies" Information: When you visit EntropiaForum, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. EntropiaForum uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to EntropiaForum. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. 

"Automatically Collected" Information: When you participate in EntropiaForum and, for example, participate in forums, control panel, profile, news, diaries, gallery or the Arcade, or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including database logging, "clear gifs" or "web beacons." This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after EntropiaForum, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit EntropiaForum.

 **THE WAY ENTROPIAFORUM USES THIS INFORMATION:**

When you choose to create a public profile on EntropiaForum, you may post, at your option, certain personal information that will be publicly displayed to other Members on EntropiaForum. EntropiaForum uses the information that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide to you all of the features and services found on EntropiaForum. We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative purposes such as sending you account activation and welcome emails, notifying you of major EntropiaForum updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement issues, or to contact you regarding any EntropiaForum activities in which you are presently participating.

EntropiaForum uses your email address to send to you activity emails, newsletters, and, from time to time, notices about special activities, features, or items available on EntropiaForum. You may opt-out of receiving such notices by indicating your preferences in the Edit Profile section of EntropiaForum. EntropiaForum uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Members, to improve the way EntropiaForum works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. 

EntropiaForum uses "automatically collected" information and "cookies" information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit EntropiaForum; (b) provide customized third-party advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of third-party marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any games, promotions, or contests. 

**WHEN ENTROPIAFORUM DISCLOSES INFORMATION:**

EntropiaForum does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your express consent. EntropiaForum may disclose "automatically collected" and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist such parties in understanding the usage and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or other functionality on EntropiaForum.   
EntropiaForum may disclose Member information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright or Criminal law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. We may make such disclosures, in some cases, without providing Members notice.   
EntropiaForum also reserves the right to disclose Member information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect EntropiaForum from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of EntropiaForum; and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of EntropiaForum, our Members, or others.

 **YOUR CHOICES:**

You may, of course, decline to share your personally-identifiable information with EntropiaForum, in which case you will not be able to participate in many EntropiaForum activities. You may update, correct, or delete your member information and email subscription preferences at any time by going to the Edit Profile section of EntropiaForum; provided, however, that upon deletion of your account or profile, please note that some of your personal information, including email address and contact information may remain in EntropiaForum's systems for some limited period of time.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections. HOWEVER, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

 **THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS, LINKS TO OTHER SITES:**

EntropiaForum allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within EntropiaForum. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear within EntropiaForum and they automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. Such third-party ad servers may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content.

EntropiaForum does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. EntropiaForum's Privacy Notice does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. EntropiaForum reserves the right the add or remove third-party ad networks or ad servers in its discretion and EntropiaForum may not at all times list such updated ad network or ad server partners in this Privacy Notice. 

Currently, EntropiaForum has relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks: 

Casale   
<http://casalemedia.com/privacy.html>

Google   
<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

Blue Lithium   
<http://www.bluelithium.com/privacy-policy.html>

**OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY:**

EntropiaForum uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to EntropiaForum, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, EntropiaForum makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If EntropiaForum learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. EntropiaForum may post a notice on EntropiaForum if a security breach occurs. 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, EntropiaForum does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on EntropiaForum from persons under 13 years-of-age, and no part of EntropiaForum is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access EntropiaForum at any time or in any manner. If EntropiaForum learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on EntropiaForum without verifiable parental consent, then EntropiaForum will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

Parents, the following are some resources that may help you in monitoring and limiting your childrens' access to certain types of material on the Internet. While EntropiaForum does not endorse these products, we provide information about them as a public service to our Members. 

Control Kids: [http://www.controlkids.com](http://www.controlkids.com/)   
Cyber Sitter: [http://www.solidoak.com](http://www.solidoak.com/)   
Net Nanny: [http://www.netnanny.com](http://www.netnanny.com/)

 **INTERNATIONAL VISITORS:**

EntropiaForum is owned and hosted in the United States and is therefore subject to United States law. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States and by providing your personal data you consent to that transfer.

 **IN THE EVENT OF MERGER OR SALE:**

In the event that EntropiaForum is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from Members as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

 **CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE:**

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by the "last modified" notice below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of EntropiaForum constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

 **EFFECTIVE DATE, DATE LAST MODIFIED:**

EntropiaForum Privacy Notice effective as of September 1, 2006.

EntropiaForum Privacy Notice last modified on September 3, 2006.

 **ENTROPIAFORUM CONTACT INFORMATION:**

Please contact EntropiaForum with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices at our [Contact Page](http://www.entropiaforum.com/forums/sendmessage.php)

* * *

_Last edited by 711 : 09-03-2006 at 08:47 AM. _
